Same shift. Different night.
Night at the Museum: Kahmunrah Rises Again is a animation,
comedy, family film directed by Matt Danner.
Nick Daley is following in his father's footsteps as night watchman at the American
Museum of Natural History, so he knows what happens when the sun goes down.
But when the maniacal ruler Kahmunrah escapes, it is up to
Nick to save the museum once and for all.
Nick Daley (voice), played by Joshua Bassett.
Teddy (voice), played by Thomas Lennon.
Kahmunrah (voice), played by Joseph Kamal.
Seth (voice), played by Akmal Saleh.
Jedediah (voice), played by Steve Zahn.
Octavius (voice), played by Jack Whitehall.
Night at the Museum: Kahmunrah Rises Again (also known as Night at the Museum 4: Kahmunrah Rises Again) is a 2022 animated fantasy comedy film directed by Matt Danner, written by Ray DeLaurentis and William
Schifrin, and starring Joshua Bassett, Jamie Demetriou, Alice Isaaz, Gillian Jacobs, Joseph Kamal, Thomas Lennon, Zachary Levi, Alexander Salamat, Kieran Sequoia, Jack Whitehall, Bowen Yang, and Steve Zahn.
The sequel to Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb (2014), it is the first animated film in the Night at the Museum film
series and the fourth installment overall, as well as the first animated feature film produced by Atomic Cartoons.
The film follows Nick Daley, the son of Larry Daley, as he becomes
a night guard at the Museum of Natural History.
In addition to Nick Daley, it also features Kahmunrah, the main antagonist
of Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian (2009).
Unlike the live-action films, 1492 Pictures is not involved with the film.
Night at the Museum: Kahmunrah Rises Again was released on December 9,
2022, on Disney+, to generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of magic, museum, mummy, pharao, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted.